I am there, it has happened,
hello,
sorry for the chilli inside, so now
what is there here, if anyone has a vehicle number, then
this playlist of Om Bolero sounds good,
someone in
Yogeshwar Dutt, friend, you download your
Muslim Bolero, should I send it to you,
tell me
write something about UP,
UP 2338 has a hidden meaning,
UP 38 piece,
I have taken out one thing in 332 9th,
half a bottle has been addressed, it has become very good,
people will automatically go for a while, okay, there is some frustration, now
here you will get its model, which
vehicle is it, what is it, what is the district end, it is
very good, everyone
takes less pressure on you, if there is any old dispute going on, let
me go to the party, brother, the
specification is old, if not, the
Aspire is broken, then it is 45 days old,
and third party, Rukhsat party, spicy Amit
Malikpur, accused third party, sometimes I want to get it done, I will
ask for the old appointed at,
I have set it with the third party,
as soon as I calculated that you are
seeing, the ID has also been admitted here, the
price is three  Lakh
22122 please like the price
of this car according to that now what is the price of this
local car, his car was priced, I got
this minimum balance brother Sadho, this
match is 3 lakh 39 thousand for both the bulls I know
jaundice has a big effect, I have done it,
I have put a pin here, the service has
decreased drastically
4272 mission completed, like complaints from
principal third party, in this also you
can send news of third party property, you
can change the behavior, you can also get passenger news
and if there is CNG and LPG then you
can add that also, okay now in this,
I sat down to drink it and saw
that now the
cost of Geet 380006 premium is 382
rupees only
38 ₹100, the 31st place is becoming back party,
its 42 ₹100 more
because there is not a big difference
welcome Wasim Bhai
if it is seen that 3800
Raghava is third party cover, his car gets stolen,
its  If the total goes then he also has
not received the money, in this his
car gets stolen in the total, so
this is the best way, if till now we have
subscribed, it
also
increases the margin for how is Lakhan Bhaiya, he has
taken the car number here, that
in the party he
presented the item number at the collectorate,
presented the budget,
took the compressive, just took the party old third,
calculated,
now see here how much is the payment in these difficult thousand increments, that is
9892, this is the picture, what is its valuation,
4,252, when the
entire storm comes, the
best Bolero in the entire state, we used to convince
all these people who used to refuse, in this way,
one small thing has to be kept in mind in this that if
anyone has any
question or any question towards such fairs, I will
tell him in the first test that
Ka Pyaar Movies Salman
Jageshwar, anyone is
giving me the name of the third party as well, it is clear
in this, I would also like to tell that I have been
stealing and there is a multi, if you say
hatred then say so,
oh sir, I just have one question  Kain
Inspector, if in the old policy
MCB is available on a strong tractor, then such
modern ones are also available or not, on this
old
tractor policy is there a 4G SIM transmitted, is
NDTV available or not, it is
definitely available in the old policy, did I
enter, but after that,
what is the last minimum volume, there is
no emptiness and scissors, tomato and back a
sense of, then where is his heart, that is a completely
different topic, right now I will talk about
this thing, both of them will be a
pair, then he would
like to talk about that, remove the big fat, the fancy belongs to
a person, not a car, that
if I sell my car,
close any setting in it, I am not interested in it, if I buy a broom, then I will get a quit, if I don't feel like
buying a car, then I can buy a broom for
NCP, then I will get a quit, if fifty percent, then I can buy a car, then fifty percent,
no, the car is yours, and if its
polyp number above the heart expires, then
even the buffalo gets destroyed, okay, if this is
that whole ocean, friends, today we will talk
first on this topic, did
someone feel something in it, or are you in it,
a question
Both these births etc. were present,
yes, you say, you say, you say, you say, you
say, if you are
making a tractor compressor, then please
click on the like button, there will be an introduction option,
for bumper-to-bumper,
you have to enter your
name and mobile number, it comes up there, I
create a customer in it because
it is
available near the subscriber,
a
picture of fuel rod and the tractor gets into an accident
and it is religious, that is
its Indian, it is formed at the back,
for transmission, electronic, if
in an accident, meter race, latest covered,
if it is excellent, then that birthday brother, right now it is a
child, it is just for tyre-tube bumper,
but right now, less than half a minute, right now I agree, but
intact engine product, I had already told you
that I will not talk to you, if there is an
introduction appeal, then there is a
time for it,
if there is anything about it,
here is the pilgrimage question, please
clear that, okay, okay, so if there is any
problem, come to the topic,
Sir, sir, sir, Manoj Kumar is talking, Sir,
wherever I live, like a bachelor, about tyres  Which has to be
taken separately if we get the vehicle
insured then when does it mean
what about the tyres and the house now come on there is no time it
is different from a car what does it mean tomorrow I do
n't have a car this is not a part of the vehicle
of course there is an option for a tractor there is a
girl he also has a girl we
talked about her text it will have to be
repaired in a separate divided centre for that
ah
I am Manoj
Yudhishthir Manoj ji
Bauji Sir even then there is
no Swapna Dosh
because there is a bumper
with it that is why it has to be taken on
auspicious occasion
if it is useless in the file then it is not there then let me
tell you that
you made a mistake
that Rupesh ji etc this
Bashir had cut the tractor because of this we did not get the
claim for this tomato from 173 company that
till now they have not given it
no how are you where are you no matter
any company in the world will
give it so I
click on the process button
[Music]
looted looted
Krishna
Radhey Radhey looted right now
take today's topic first topic
in answer to one of your questions
my mobile number you have
both the options this is a festival
This is a festival, isn't it,
Pimple caught,
robbers, inter college
function, mute the distance, let's go to
Chandigarh, tell me the method of joining the shine, you
can come out completely, if the answer is
not in returning the payment, then the
bhajans of my cars, I bought a cup of
water, I bought a car, Chand 2016
model, okay, I also took care of the car, chose it,
left it, picked it up and gave it to Lakshmi, after
six months, after 7 minutes, I
picked it up, put it in a bowl and how
many are there in the juice of inch, 70% of those who
come are road, 70% of this is produced
only 10 per cent, lovers celebrate, I have
many such cancers which I settle by sitting with the
survey, there are
many such clans like my victory, this
tractor power comes to me, I don't need anyone, I am not doing
anything, but the same thing is that
in their head, more and more I feel like the
stomach will be sent, so
first the stuffing
part
and after 2 minutes, tell me which
reader is unbreakable, how will you break it, how will it break
Leave it side by side hello yes batting a hello hello
for that we will take these general photos, it is a
mandate to have PAN card number
and when we create this then the
photos of the vehicle, is it a general 31 vehicle
or not I had said that it took 5 minutes
or we get it from someone so to
stop the questions this is the trick to
ask for photos and life photos from the company I have
updated it, I will
make Jannat party in black TV, listen 119
Bolero Scorpio price is for these four models
so now the question is see, in pot planning we
understand a little bit, the rest of the time we
don't get the picture, the whole picture is very little understood, when we do
something then your father
will do 119, so
when we do one of them then
you
Shubhendu just talk to me once so that I can
come to you Malik only then which way you refuse, you already do it, neither Bajaj does it, neither
SBI does it, neither
ICC does it, nor ABC does it,
how many of their total are there that are government companies  It
is difficult to make
that Iqbal Singh Dhindsa had to make it, he
knows that half an hour, one hour the main thing got spoiled,
one hour my Bhola Bhaiya, there is an embarrassing aspect in this
and that is why he made this statement, the best
statement you can make in it, so
this was from one side
in Galaxy, his acting, it means this related to anyone would have happened
first, after which he
patted
this question, hey friend, it's a
very cute photo,
why didn't you get it today, then he took it down Galaxy, no
one has any problem, it has been sent to everyone,
hey friend, I had placed the last order,
you love, you should go out and ask, are you
taking tension,
plug feel Mukhtiar,
I am laughing, don't let it go, I know, then
ask later, who will eat it, come and ask, right now, what will happen,
Raghavan,
I have just made some memories, so the same things are
that
now you have the
facility to get third party insurance for this Bolero
and you can do
that today this is the only question which I
want to talk about in Galaxy, the rest which is not there right now, do
not go down below
Tell me,
waste some time too, sir, whatever
you did not get, there is
total dry ginger stolen
and
a cotton part was tied.